[Music]
show me freely
hmm
now we have both learned something I am
grateful for what we have taught each
other I do not punish when one seeks
forgiveness I envy EDS
for their Clarity of purpose perhaps I
can share your burden there is a new
sadness in you brother yes we wondered
how many other omnics were doing the
same
change often comes Uninvited what you
make of it is up to you every challenge
is an opportunity to rise I am happy to
serve
interesting a chance for us all to learn
experience
festivity
right down the middle
and the pitch
here's a little chin music that's the
ball game
there is no crying in baseball you're
out he goes down swinging it goes down
swinging
she goes down swinging Zenyatta on the
mound
the iris consumes you
listen to The Whispers of Madness
Darkness envelops all
be consumed by the Shadows
curses and Madness be upon you all
be one with the darkness
walk in Shadow
we walk in the shadows my Apprentice
Embrace Oblivion
frightening
experience nothingness
trick or treat
pass into the unknown
Zenyatta is here
Zenyatta is everywhere
we must guard the objective they have
taken possession of him
he will be lost without our guidance
the enemy has stolen away our friend
our teammate has fallen we have suffered
a casualty we have lost a teammate the
door will not hold much longer the door
will soon be reduced to kindling I am
restored
you have my thanks one day I will repay
your kindness
who
it was nothing you are welcome a turret
lies before us
it is quite real a turret lies in our
way
we must proceed as one apart we cannot
continue we must come together then we
may proceed the payload is on its way
the payload advances as it should I am
accompanying the payload we must halt
the payload I am under attack
assistance would be appreciated
I require Aid on my way no we must rest
Victory from the jaws of time time is an
illusion but the illusion is about to
run out no snowflake ever falls in the
wrong place we are in harmony
doubt shrouds you what torments you it
is nothing personal Genji why the look
of Gloom
your distress betrays you such a a
shadow hangs over you
your anguish consumes you
you must accept the pain this does not
bode well for you
chaos haunts your path the path ahead is
thorny how ominous
attachment is the source of all
suffering
revive me so that I may rejoin the fight
I am in need of Reviving
I am seriously damaged life is more than
a series of ones and zeros
we must protect our flag defend our flag
a Detonator approaches we must not let
it come near the end approaches quickly
to the robot our time draws near grasp
the opportunity we must claim both the
robot and our destiny
our Collective effort is leading us to
Victory let us be grateful for our
advantages
Fortune Smiles on us a blessing to be
among such capable hands we should make
our preparations here
oh
we must clear this area
form is temporary the spirit is eternal
my apologies I was mistaken to air is
human or omnic I require armor I need
armor we must deal with this assassin
she continues to be a problem for us
we must take the objective let us
capture the objective
the enemy's teleporter is here
destroy it my ultimate ability is ready
ready for Transcendence the enforcer
still poses a threat the flag's Destiny
lies with another
dropping the flag
Zenyatta is here advance the robot move
the robot
the flag returns I have set the flag on
its way the Assassin is over there
she is but intimidating nonetheless get
back
she is on me in three two one
three two one
get ready
no
oh
let us push together
and now we begin
Destiny beckons us toward our
destination
My ultimate is charging
[Music]
no
hello world
the Assassin is no more worry not she
has been dealt with
defend as one
defend with me alone I am attempting
Target for the enemy our numbers will
soon be replenished my allies will soon
return
farewell go in peace I have found the
enemy Shield generator My ultimate is
almost ready
understood
acknowledged of course
indeed I understand understood
the door shutters
the door is heavily damaged this life is
not finished with you yet we are still
in need of you
invisibility is not invincibility you
manifested your own Fate One often meets
their Destiny on the road they take to
avoid it those who Rush head long into
battle would do well to protect their
heads a great distance for one is but a
step for another think first then leap
an easy target is not always what it
appears to be
foresight is as valuable as speed ask
for death and you will receive it
remember Genji at your most powerful you
are most vulnerable Capture the Flag let
us take the enemy's flag be reborn
Oblivion Embraces you
Fade Into shadow
May the iris embrace you be at peace
the wheel turns
the darkness consumes let us clear them
off the objective our enemies are
seizing the objective they are taking
hold of the objective we must stop them
fortune favors me
[Laughter]
the iris Embraces you
it is my pleasure to serve there is no
weakness in asking for help those who
seek help will find it consider the
alternative
The World Is A Dangerous Place
the help is its own reward how amusing
the end is near we must not hold back
time grows short attack we must rest
Victory from the jaws of time time is an
illusion but the illusion is about to
run out press forward for time is not on
our side time is of the essence let us
attack an Eradicator be on your guard
she still poses a threat the sniper
still troubles us
can I interest you in a snowball fight
do I think does a submarine swim
the turret no longer exists the turret
is no more the objective cannot take
much more of this our objective will
soon be destroyed Mercy swiftly
delivered the more one takes the less
one has
accomplishment always follows effort
tragedy unites many my generosity
extends to many perhaps we only exist in
the memory of a person now gone
ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha
you're right
patience the damage doesn't look as bad
from up here
[Music]
the objective is no more
the objective has been eliminated I
require Shields I need Shields the
Assassin is gone for the moment
she has disappeared Victory is our
destiny but we must all play our parts
stay steadfast and we shall win
Victory is within our grasp hold strong
we must see this through to the end let
us hold out until the end
time is on our side we must simply
endure I am feeling unwell my systems
are compromised disabling security
protocols your recognition honors me
the cards have selected me our enemies
return with a Vengeance beware they have
returned
the enemy is utilizing a shield
generator enemy Shield generator
destroyed
halt the robot we must end their push
recover our flag
we must retake possession of our flag
peace be upon you
I greet you hello
greetings we must reclaim our flag the
enemy has taken possession of our flag
come to me for healing come here for
healing the path to Healing Leads Here a
shock Tire Bears down upon us
shock Tire over the bridge the enemy
possesses a teleporter energy transfers
between us I believe I've won this round
a telling blow a touch of wisdom what
profound impact
Scottish
foreign
[Music]
over here
I have spotted an enemy Bastion remember
past successes but always strive for
more
this way here my friends
I am vitalized
my senses are heightened
strength flows through me
I am empowered
I think
therefore I am when did you receive this
curse Countess some believe that the
full moon is a good omen
did I say I trusted her I do not sense
the spark of life within you walk along
the path to Enlightenment ready I am
ready I dreamed I was a butterfly
frightening there are no Troopers ahead
no Trooper spotted the enforcer is no
more the flag moves with me I have
become one with the flag go to the
objective
let us head to the Waypoint let us
regroup at the objective
the objective is near
take care that you do not spend yourself
before the battle is done our purpose is
to show everyone that in the iris We Are
All One People
rarely has my path crossed a warrior as
cheerful as you no one of note just one
of thousands like me do you think me so
helpless but One Moment of clarity
changed everything
there are times even I cannot stand by
it is not magic but the power of the
spirit that I Channel my beliefs are
simply in the fundamental ways of life
and nature nothing more
simply a traveler in search of purpose
and meaning
I am following in my Master's footsteps
searching for enlightenment though my
path has not always been a straight one
our objective has been damaged our
enemies are breaking through
fate is not without a sense of irony
look in the mirror we move with the
objective
let us see the objective to its
destination
the enemy outnumbers us we are
outnumbered be cautious I sense the
Reaper I sense the presence of the Witch
the Summoner is here Dr junkenstein
so good of you to join us
the ground shakes
junkenstein's Monster is here
we should guide our flag back to safety
the enemy has relinquished our flag we
must move them from the door
they have reached the door
the Summoner is no more
the witch is gone
but she will return
Dr junken Stein has laughed his last
junkenstein's monster Has Fallen the
reaper is gone
for the moment
I am made whole
my systems are restored
my systems are repaired
I am healed your dance grows more
elegant Satya you are Adept at endings
well done my Apprentice
eventually all Fade Into Oblivion
well done Genji you have ushered them to
Oblivion
there is Beauty in your actions I did
not teach you that one fall back
likewise Sacha I hope to repay you for
your generosity at our Temple I served
coffee then painted with emptiness how
fortunate for you
why do you believe so I collected
payments at a laser tag arena perhaps
they believe we will not defend this
place
but if all the rest of the world were to
fall this would be the stand I chose to
make I like being near the ocean it
reminds me of where I was born
I sense that your heart is Battle Is Yet
To Come
what seems like magic is sometimes
science we don't yet understand
Victory goes to those who maintain their
focus
I was a lifeguard at a water park it
will be a pleasure I drove a tractor you
have an intense gays doctor you spend
your second chance at life walking a
lonely road
I believe that torbjorn's behavior has
rubbed off on you
I owe my gifts to the iris what makes
you think I am a pacifist someone always
cares you must simply seek them out I
dream of peace
and sometimes falling and yet you sound
just like he did a mirror reflects only
what can be seen Perhaps it is
assumptions that are foolish
try listening to silence our mission
awaits us
indeed I massaged sheep on a free-range
pasture shed the weight of your doubts
and your mind will become clear
seeking progress by sowing chaos is like
planting a tree in a volcano change
often comes Uninvited what you make of
it is up to you quite a puzzle isn't it
I embrace the unknown
and what of the Enemy Within I focus on
my breathing
strangeness is in the eye of the
beholder
my memories from before the Awakening
are blurry like a fading dream
but I do remember some things in the
coming battle you mean
to find success we must search in
harmony
as long as there is Free Will I fear
there will be evil if a city never
sleeps
how can it dream those who seek only to
enrich themselves live the most
impoverished lives of all
true it also makes us great teachers for
we can easily hide our disappointment
indeed why are we here ask not who their
maker is but what they mean
is Victory so important
fruition comes from within
as does failure
I have always wondered what it is like
being inside an orb over there I need
help
I require assistance I pray that we can
reverse this outcome we are not defeated
yet we must persevere through the
difficult times
this obstacle can still be overcome
trick or treat a temporary setback we
can overcome any obstacle we must act
and soon
let us remember our purpose progress
awaits us
perhaps we are forgetting something we
must eliminate this target caution be
alert watch here an enemy here
here is an enemy heed this one we must
guard the objective defend the objective
even the teacher can learn from his
student it takes a hundred times to
learn
a thousand times to understand
one who fears loss has already lost the
cycle begins anew true strength does not
always lie in Victory pain is an
excellent teacher
overconfidence is a flimsy Shield a
reminder that life is never easy
defeat cannot break one who perseveres
Michael is broken
adversity is an opportunity for change a
challenge presents itself a temporary
setback
failure is acceptable giving up is not
the outcome is not preordained
repetition is the path to Mastery our
Fates are Written in the Stars
the enemy is here the enemy desires a
battle let the blessings of the Season
be upon you
I return
press the attack let us all become one
with the objective
proceed to the objective an enforcer is
before us pass into the iris
reflect upon your actions your setback
is only temporary rest your soul a cruel
fate Pride cannot protect you your focus
lacks Focus one day you will see that
coming
science cannot answer all questions
and now you have found peace
you must learn from your mistakes
no fist has ever won against an open
hand your answer lies in Stillness
good judgment comes from bad experiences
regret is all-consuming a resolution
swiftly delivered all ice melts a
beautiful swan song I didn't go easy on
you this time
and so the mask Falls
we all represent unfulfilled potential
greed has spent you silence answers all
questions a closed mind is already
defeated
let the sun set on your pride defeat is
the better teacher what goes around
comes around
not everything should be taken seriously
when you soar you risk the fall
move too quickly and you overlook much
what Legacy is worth your life
in chaos more chaos
do not hesitate the lead awaits us
soon the lead will be ours we are being
drawn to the lead
though I stand alone my teammates still
fight at my side the task Falls to me we
are making progress upon the objective
the objective has taken damage all
proceeds according to plan
the rhythm is in you if you search
within get down into the iris float to
the beat
um
embrace the Rhythm embrace the beat
embrace the melody move your feet
I humbly accept I will become one with
this reward
the universe shares its Bounty I foresee
great riches in my future
the experience is its own reward
but surprises are nice
join me
group up group up here
we must join as one
group up with me
join together
I will not juggle yes the door has
opened to our enemy the enemy comes
through the doorway We Must Destroy the
objective
focus our attacks upon the objective
that was your lesson for today our
moments run out do not leave him
now we must Focus stay with our robot
friend I can sense your presence enemy
detected there is someone there let go
of that which weighs upon your mind
behind you slicers approaching
laughs
join me at the objective
come to the objective to me my friends
what joy to share the path with another
a promising disciple
you've learned well Genji our minds
aligned it takes two hands to clap a
meaningful Union what intention many
hands we must focus our attack upon the
objective I see the sniper there she is
I will watch this place keeping watch
here
allow me to watch here meditation is all
I require to sustain myself
it must be my many years of training
careful diet and simple way of life
you wound me a pause in the battle an
opportunity to re-center our minds when
I gazed into the iris I found a great
nothingness
it changed me
you must have experienced the same you
blame yourself for the dragon's Reign of
Terror but it is not your fault push
forward
they have all perished we are alone
for now
Serenity at last
free your mind
the enemy stirs we must halt them
do not allow the enemy to proceed the
enemy begins to move along their path
reach the door and our path will be
revealed we must break through
remove the obstruction before us
focus on the target we must eliminate
this target
through here
our path lies this way
I have dropped the item
unfortunately I dropped it I sense an
enemy to the right a shock Tire
approaches on our right
Joy to the World
we must locate their teleporter a shock
Tire approaches on the left our enemy
approaches on the left I welcome
adversity a momentary setback
my thanks
thank you
I am grateful you have my thanks
wonderful
Excellence is its own reward get out of
there I am going in we have injured the
heavy assault unit a chance presents
itself to strike him down
Talent Trooper engaging I see a sniper
sniper
hmm
always strive for improvement together
we have taken the lead
ah progression
we advance as one
your flaws are revealed in the iris
know when to hold on and when to let go
how far the Mighty Fall
a stumble is still a step towards a
direction a fall is merely a chance to
rise again
later
observe your environment carefully you
may be missed but not by me what is
dissent but a lesson in humility they
have fallen how unfortunate attack let
us strike in harmony attack with me
[Music]
amid Discord we will find Tranquility he
must be dealt with we must find a way to
deal with the heavy assault unit the
summoner's threat must be ended Dr
junken Stein must be dealt with
the reaper still haunts us we must
banish the witch
junkenstein's monster must be destroyed
existence is mysterious I have learned
from my experiences
my mind is open my spirit is strong now
to strike energy flows through me every
rooster crows in its own pen
hello
oh
the payload is at a standstill let us
push the payload forward we must unblock
the payload incoming
the payload Must Be Stopped we must
hinder the payloads journey let us halt
that payload I require healing I need
healing
how
disappointing
she has turned her attention to you the
Assassin is targeting you take cover
Victory or defeat our destiny is not
preordained
be present in the moment
it is good to return but am I still
welcome here your will is strong my
friend but in time I know you will
realize we are not so different and I
will watch your back in turn
consider only Victory make defeat an
impossibility in your mind
tell me your thoughts my friend
I can feel the Embrace of the iris so
strongly here
I would be happy to teach you it is rare
that I meet one with such an unformed
mind it is good to fight alongside one
of my brightest pupils it does my
brother mandata gave much to improve
their lives
but it was not to be
a disciplined mind is your most
Dependable Ally a chance to focus A
Warrior's greatest weapon
is patience so this is where you grew up
you must show me around if only human
and omnic could learn to live in peace
here
I sense within you the same rage that
once consumed your brother what a
fascinating place
can science alone unlock the path to
Enlightenment do you have any dreams my
friend and I do not understand much of
how you heal Dr Ziegler
I suppose we must all take some things
on faith existence
mysterious isn't it
an omnic on the moon is not so special
there are more robots than humans in
space to us all I miss him greatly I
believe that we must all do our part to
find solutions to the troubles that are
before us it is sad to see a place that
might have known peace reduced to this a
noble but tragic sacrifice
I hope that you will honor it I have not
returned here for many years I wonder if
my brothers and sisters will be pleased
to see me Turing green
my brother's dream
but not to be
time is a river it may be stopped for a
while but it will always flow the same
direction
I feel most unwelcome here
Genji how was your reunion with your
brother
symmetra you speak of Law and of order
but you must know that life is chaotic
by its very nature I believe that you
could find peace if you were to search
within yourself
indeed my friend indeed I hear that you
have taken in an omnic torbjorn the
payload rests Idol the payload must be
moved we must move the payload
this will be of use I have what we seek
here we are I sense the presence of an
assassin an assassin comes for us
experience tranquility
our teammate is in need of Reviving
our teammate needs to be revived
let us pave our path together
shall we journey together we must work
and breathe as one we are all pilgrims
on this Mission I am with you we are as
one the path of Fate threatens to
diverge in the enemy's favor
the enemy draws near
stop them we must prevent the enemy from
taking the lead the objective nears
destruction
we have almost achieved our objective
the enemy has pushed past us we have
lost the lead the enemy's understanding
surpasses ours the enemy's teleporter is
no more I feel the darkness flowing
through me
my soul ignited I am effervescent my
spirit Burns an or14 engage with caution
remember me for I Will Remember You
my heavy burden to bear
virtuosity is an admirable virtue a
Herald of Victory
Mastery cannot be concealed our enemy
gathers here I shall handle this it is
done
allow me we must see this through to the
end
Victory is our destiny but we must all
play our parts
Victory is within our grasp hold strong
I am in agreement we need a Healer the
enemy's flag is ours I have captured the
flag if you do not change direction you
may end up where you're headed let us
escort you along your path we will unify
our push with yours hello brother
come with us go I am attaining the
objective I am on the objective my
friends join me on the objective death
is Whimsical today walk in Shadow
listen to my prayer Harmony is within
your grasp be whole once more
I release your suffering a balm for your
wounds we walk in the shadows my
Apprentice gaze into the unblinking eye
Embrace Oblivion
be one with the darkness
be reassured You Are Not Alone
find Solace
overcome your pain
your spirits lifted let me assist you
allow me
Harmony follows you
be soothed I am with you my friend
let me relieve your burdens
no no
no
I'm over here
I am here
My ultimate is ready proceed without
fear
you are not ready to learn
peace and blessings be upon you all
oh
[Music]
the attack comes from above
the attack comes from the right our
enemies are behind us they attack from
below our enemies attack from the rear
the enemy lies before us our enemies
attack directly the enemy is on the left
the enemy is below us the enemy is above
us
the enemy is on the right the attack
comes from the left one Moon shows in
every pool in every pool the one Moon